the military found out about brain
organoid computation I was curious about
what kind of projects the military is
working on right now and I looked
through DARPA and I found something
interesting they've been studying
organoids on a chip since
2012 I'm having a little bit of an
existential crisis right now that is
long before anyone ever put them in a
spider drone yeah that that's the spider
drone I love it do you remember the
Australian company that's immersed them
in Game World and by having them play
Pong and learn it they decided they were
that was funded by the Australian
military and that was very recent as for
the year 2023 which is not classified in
DARPA they've been studying brain
organoids for the purpose of treating
traumatic brain injuries and medicine
and we as a human species are getting
really good at using the brain organoids
to treat Strokes better every time I see
a favor come out and there is no
information out there that I can find on
what's going on with the brain organoid
on a chip research for the US military
let me be clear there is no second place
we already know that they've been
invested heavily in controlling drones
with AI 2012 was before I graduated high
school there has got to be a brain
organoid and a drone out there there
just has to be and yeah it is really
cool that we're thinking about applying
these to traumatic brain injuries but
come on the Australian government is
just honest about it I I want to see the
brain drone